From Daily Wire published March
20th 2026 Iranian leaders we
have the Americans exactly where
we want them Iranian leaders we
we want them The only thing
keeping the American war effort
alive is the fact that the
French have refused to join the
fight Mar 20th 2026 DailyWire
com Listen to this article Ada
Kanar AFP via Getty Images
According to the New York Times
a former newspaper American
forces are in deep trouble in
Iran as the wily Iranians
continue to attack our bombs
with their leaders According to
the Times Middle East Bureau
chief Omar Jihad Mohamed Jihad
Mohamed wave after wave of
American bomb and missile
attacks have been repelled by an
iron dome of Iranian leaders so
that the weapons explode
harmlessly against their bodies
destroying nothing but the
Iranian army Air Force Navy
missiles drones radar and of
course the Iranian leaders Who
are more than willing to
sacrifice their lives to protect
those Iranian people they
haven't yet murdered themselves
In an exclusive interview at an
undisclosed location the New
York Times Middle East reporter
Omar Jihad Mohamed Fatwa Mohamed
interviewed Iran's chief of
police Fatwa Mohamed Jihad Omar
Mamdani who said we have the
Americans exactly where we want
them since And while he was
unable to finish his sentence
because he was assassinated by
Israeli defense forces he was
immediately replaced by his
younger subordinate Allahu Akbar
Mohamed Tucker Jihad Jihad
Mohamed who said as my
predecessor was about to explain
but he was unable to finish his
sentence because he was
assassinated by Israeli defense
forces According to either
Iranian officials or CNN
reporters it's difficult to tell
the difference Iran continues to
stymie American attacks so that
the only thing keeping the
American war effort alive is the
fact that the French have
refused to join the fight So
there's no one who will
surrender for us And now the
Iranians have achieved a
stunning moral victory according
to CNN chief Middle East
correspondent Vladimir Mohamed
Jihad Death to America Carlson
Mohamed Fatwa In a move
reflecting the enduring strength
of the Iranian regime the nation
has replaced the 15 levels of
leadership who were wiped out by
American and Israeli attacks by
appointing as their new supreme
leader Mojtaba Khamenei a one
legged homosexual who's in a
coma President of the Academy of
Motion Picture Arts and Sciences
Mohamed Jinping Fatwa Bernie
Sanders Jihad celebrated the
appointment of Khamenei saying
this is a tremendous leap
forward for Iranian diversity
equity and inclusion By
selecting an unconscious
handicapped gay man to
ruthlessly oppress their people
Iran has installed an Ayatollah
who looks exactly like the sort
of person for whom Hollywood has
been making movies We hope this
will encourage more people to
become one legged comatose
homosexuals so we can begin to
fill up our theaters Otherwise
there'll be no one there to see
it when Nicole Kidman finally
manages to move her face again
American branches of the
organization Queers for
Palestine also celebrated the
appointment of the gay Ayatollah
with queer house parties across
the nation at which they honored
Islamic tradition by climbing up
to the rooftops and hurling
themselves to their deaths As
Queer for Palestine leader
Anatole Preposterous announced
to his fellow queers Iran has
struck a blow against the
homophobic splat Although I'm
not sure if that was the last
word in the sentence or just the
sound he made when he hit the
pavement The organization
Feminists for Palestine was also
pleased by the Ayatollah's
appointment FFP president Sally
Ann Preposterous no relation
said although we're disappointed
Iran has not yet elevated a
woman to leadership as feminists
we feel that a homosexual in a
coma will at least represent
people who hate women without
thinking which is what feminism
is all about As for the new
Ayatollah though he has not yet
been able to issue a statement
of his own the regime has
released some of the old
messages he posted on the
website sleepinggayamputees com
which include such remarks as
must have good sense of humor
and if you like my picture swipe
right Meanwhile according to PBS
Middle East reporter Mohammad
Mamdani Jihad Tucker Tucker
fatwa jihad global financial
markets continue to reel at the
plucky Iranian attacks on the
Strait of Hormuz PBS interviewed
surviving Iranian naval
commander Mohammad Jihad Fuentes
Fatwa Carlson who said we will
continue to attack shipping here
until but he was unable to
finish his sentence because he
was assassinated by Israeli
defense forces This excerpt is
taken from the opening satirical
monologue of the Andrew Clavon
show Andrew Clavon is the host
of the Andrew Clavon show at the
Daily Wire Clavon is the
bestselling author of numerous
books including the Cameron
Winter Mystery series The fifth
installment after that The Dark
is now available Follow him on X
The views expressed in this
satirical piece are those of the
author and do not necessarily
represent those of the Daily
Wire